# Simon Baey

## Senior Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

Rich experience in web development working on a variety of projects at several companies using modern frameworks like React, Typescript, Next, and Node. An important problem solver in the teams and never failed to deliver quality work with my hard work and soft skills. Career as a lead developer in some project and company. My products are always designed with user convenience and performance in mind, and I work honestly with them.



6206524456



Englewood, CO, US

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Full Stack & Blockchain Engineer self-employed

07/2022 - Present

- Built the many Solana NFT minting, staking, game sites using React, TypeScript, Web3 and Rust and Candy Machine.
- Built the NFT minting and Dapp site using React, TypeScript, Web3, Solidity, Smart Contract and upgraded V1 to V3.

# Senior Full Stack & Blockchain Engineer CryptoTag

11/2020 - 07/2022

- Built the DeFi using React, TypeScript, Web3 for the frontend and Solidity, Hardhat, Truffle for the Smart Contract.
- Built the NFT marketplace using React, Typescript, Web3, ASP.NET, C#, Solidity and MongoDB, GraphQL on the EVM network as a senior developer with the team.
- Built the DEX for individual customer using React, Typescript, Nest.js and Solidity with 3 team members as a lead developer.

# Senior Front End Developer

#### Bitwage

09/2019 - 10/2020

- Built the simple swap site using React, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Web3 and utilized the various API such as REST API, Fast API, Twitter and so on.
- Improved SEO using Next.js and built the NFT minting sites using React, Web3, TypeScript, Solidity.
- Led 5 new junior developers on team in expanding React and TypeScript.

## Front End Developer Nimble

05/2017 - 06/2019

- Built the various CRM sites and financial sites using React, TypeScript, Node.js, Material UI and Styled Components.
- Built 12+ projects using CMS platform such as BigCommerce, WooCommerce, WordPress, Shopify and so on.
- Built the business and game sites such as shopping, restaurant using React, WordPress, Shopify, MongoDB, MySQL, and three.js.
- Built a Real Estate site using Next.is, React, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript, Sanity CMS and Firebase and built the mobile chat app using React Native and Socket.io

# **Full Stack Developer**

#### PeopleSearch

03/2015 - 04/2017

- Worked with designers to resolve UI/UX problems, improve operations, and provided exceptional customer service.
- Built the hockey game site using Angular, TypeScript, Laravel, and MySQL and built the environmental site using MERN, MEAN stack.

## **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Sundrip

- https://dapp-prestaging.sundrip.io/
- Used technologies: React, TypeScript, ASP.NET, C#, Solidity, AWS.

#### Best day

- https://www.bestday.com.mx/
- Used technologies: React, TypeScript. Node/Express, MongoDB.

#### Hockey

- https://d5.hockeyshare.com/
- Used technologies: Angular, TypeScript, PHP(Laravel), MySQL.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Computer Science** Singapore Management University

04/2010 - 07/2014

- Bachelor's Degree